## **PROFILE**

Anupam Shringi is a senior manager within center of data & insights team of Accenture Applied Intelligence and has 14+ years of experience in championing data driven insights, cloud-based technologies and developing products using multiple external data sources.

He has helped sell and deliver high profile digital transformation projects across the globe spanning multiple industries. He also has significant international exposure including a 3-year stint at Accenture Hong Kong.

He has worked across industries such as retail, banking, public services, telecom and consumer goods.

### CONTACT

PHONE: +91-9611997500

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anupam-shringi-93a2785/

FMAII:

ashringi@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**



# ANUPAM SHRINGI

SENIOR ANALYTICS CONSULING MANAGER, ACCENTURE

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE (KEY HIGHLIGHTS)**

#### **ACCENTURE, Senior Analytics Consulting Manager**

New Delhi, Hong Kong, San Francisco, Bangalore May 2010 - Present

- Grew the public services pod from scratch to a **20-member** team in a span of 6 months
- Led and supported sales of multiple government cloud, data and analytics transformation winning deals close to \$5M in just the last quarter.
- Co-led the development of data driven customer experience analyzer product which led to 20+ client deals across, retail, health, consumer goods, banking, etc.
- Championed the use of **unified cloud infrastructure** and reduced dependence on multiple licensed tools.
- Led the delivery of an innovative digital prospect 360 for a US digital only bank using multiple third-party data sources to personalize and prioritize personal loan targeting resulting in 60% decrease in cost per acquisition
- Led a team of consultants in a pilot project for a Hong Kong banking client delivering a 3X response rate over the existing campaign using analytics driven marketing strategy leading to a multi-year deal with the client.
- Delivered valuable marketing insights by analyzing billions of credit card transactions per day using big data technologies such as Hadoop, Hive, etc. for a large US payment gateway provider in USA. Helped the client in integrating the data from various sources such as web, airlines, hotel booking data
- Delivered data strategy roadmap & analytics driven
  Campaign design for large Indian insurance client using machine learning models to identify the customers who are most likely to buy certain insurance products.

#### Capillary Technologies, Customer success Manager

Hong Kong & Bangalore Sep 2015 to Mar 2016

> Capture real time customer POS data and manage loyalty programs and analytics for leading Hong Kong and Indian Apparel brands

#### **EDUCATION**

### Indian Institute of Technology Kharagpur

2004-2008

Civil engineering major from one of the leading technical universities in India. Won multiple music and theatre competitions

•